<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<index version="1" name="MXM Scripts">
  <category name="Scripts">
    <reapack name="mxm_List of Instruments and Effects.lua" type="script" desc="List of Instruments and Effects">
      <metadata>
        <description><![CDATA[{\rtf1\ansi\deff0\nouicompat{\fonttbl{\f0\fnil\fcharset238 Arial;}{\f1\fnil\fcharset2 Symbol;}}
{\*\generator Riched20 10.0.19041}\viewkind4\uc1 
\pard\sa200\sl276\slmult1\f0\fs22\lang5 This is a Lua script, which lists all Reaper plugins used in an active project, grouping them into categories. The motivation comes from KVR OSC (KVRaudio One Synth Challange) competition, which requires providing technical details of the production.\par

\pard\sa200\sl240\slmult1 When running the script, it immediately shows results in the opened window. Further, it provides a few buttons allowing copying the result to the clipboard. Currently available options are:\par

\pard{\pntext\f1\'B7\tab}{\*\pn\pnlvlblt\pnf1\pnindent0{\pntxtb\'B7}}\fi-360\li720\sa200\sl240\slmult1 Plain text - it's the text shown in the preview window\par
{\pntext\f1\'B7\tab}Markdown - results are formatted into tables using markdown syntax\par
{\pntext\f1\'B7\tab}BB plain - results use some BBcode formatting, like bold\par
{\pntext\f1\'B7\tab}BB [code] - results are enclosed into [CODE] [/CODE] BBcode tags, to force fixed-width fonts\par

\pard\sa200\sl240\slmult1 Note, that every press of Copy to clipboard button generates the report again, including a refresh of displayed content. Normally the report shown in the script window is plain text, regardless format selected by pressing the export button. With the debug checkbox checked, the report shown in the window will be the same as the content copied into the clipboard.\par
}
]]></description>
      </metadata>
      <version name="1.0" author="Michal MaXyM Bartak" time="2023-11-11T21:01:00+01:00">
        <changelog><![CDATA[Initial version]]></changelog>
        <source main="main">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/michalk-k/ListOfInstrumentsAndEffects/main/scripts/mxm/mxm_List%20of%20Instruments%20and%20Effects.lua</source>
      </version>
      <version name="2.0" author="Michal MaXyM Bartak" time="2024-01-12T20:00:00+01:00">
        <changelog><![CDATA[Added GUI and options to copy result to clipboard in various formats]]></changelog>
        <source main="main">https://raw.githubusercontent.com/michalk-k/ListOfInstrumentsAndEffects/gui_added/scripts/mxm/mxm_List%20of%20Instruments%20and%20Effects.lua</source>
      </version>
    </reapack>
  </category>
  <metadata>
    <description></description>
  </metadata>
</index>

